Privacy Policy
==============

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you use TrueVPNreviews (“our Site”), you will be regarded as having read and accepted this Privacy Policy. If you don’t wish to be bound by what you read below, you shouldn’t use our Site.

Our Privacy Policy explains

1. What information we collect and how we collect it
2. How we use that information
3. How to find out more about our policies

This is a very important policy page and we hope you will read it carefully.

### **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We do not ask you or anyone else to give us any personal information in order to use TrueVPNreviews.

We do collect anonymised information to provide a better service to all our users – from improving our less popular pages to tracking the commissions that allow the site to operate as a free resource.

Under no circumstances we will ask you any personal information of yours such as your email, name, telephone number and so on.

### **Site Analytics**

Every time anyone visits our Site, we collect anonymised information about that visit. Like most big websites, we do this through Google Analytics software to better understand how people use our site. While we do not use Google Analytics to collect any personally identifying information (such as name or address), we do collect the following kinds of information:

* The pages you visit on TrueVPNreviews.net
* How long you spend on each page of our Site
* How you got to our Site
* What kind of device you were using
* Your home country and browser settings such as language

We also sometimes use other third-party analytics tools, such as Hotjar, that collect information about how you interact with our Site, such as what you click on and the parts of the page you spend most time on.

We use this information to better understand our customers and their needs in order to improve our service.

This information is anonymized and cannot be tied back to any individual.

This anonymized analytics information is stored behind secure log-ins that can only be accessed by TrueVPNReviews.net employees using their official credentials.

### **Cookies and similar technologies**

Like most websites, TrueVPNReviews puts small files (known as ‘cookies’) onto your computer to collect information about how you browse our Site.

You can read our cookie policy for a detailed breakdown of the types of cookie we use and why we use them.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not, and by allowing us to earn commissions.

A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you. You can choose to accept or decline cookies through your browser settings. Look at aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance about how to do this.

We may implement third party advertising or other content on the Site that may use clear gifs or other forms of web beacons, which allow the third party content provider to read and write Cookies to your web browser in connection with your viewing of the third party content on the Site.

Additionally, we may implement third party buttons (such as Facebook “like” or “share” buttons) that may allow a third party to collect information about you through their browser Cookies, even when you do not interact with the button.

Information collected through web beacons and buttons is collected directly by third parties, and TrueVPNReviews does not participate in that data transmission. Information collected by a third party in this manner is subject to that third party’s own data collection, use, and disclosure policies.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**
---------------------------

TrueVPNReviews contains links to other websites.

This privacy policy only applies to this website, and doesn’t cover other sites that we link to. If you go to another website, read the privacy policy on that website to find out what it does with your information.

**CHANGES**
-----------

We may, from time to time, update this Privacy Policy to reflect any changes to our privacy practices in accordance with changes to legislation, best practice or enhancements to TrueVPNReviews. We will let you know what these changes are by posting them to this page, but it is your responsibility as a user to make sure that you are aware of them, by checking for any changes on a regular basis. Changes will become effective as soon as they are posted.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**
---------------------

If you have any questions about our cookies or this policy, please contact us at [info(@)truevpnreviews.net](#) and we will get back to you within two working days.

**Last updated: 04/10/2019**

We are committed to provide you with honest reviews, always unbiased. We would never "sell" for any amount to simply increase our rating or our view for any VPN provider.

#### Contact

#### About

[TrueVPNreviews.net](https://truevpnreviews.net/) | © 2024. All rights reserved.

Search for:
